Guide to the Wilfrid S. Sellars Papers, 1899-1990 ASP.1991.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research and Writing, 1925-1990; II.
  - Manuscripts of Other Authors, 1925-1990; 3.
    - Quittes, John, "Thought and Language: Reflections on Sellars' Theory of Intentionality", 1980s (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Raab, Francis
      - "Blanshard's Theory of Free Will", c. 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - "The Concept of Responsibility", undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - "History, Determinism, and Responsibility", c. 1956 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - "History, Freedom, and Responsibility", c. 1955 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - "Intention as a Criterion of Responsibility", undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Railton, Peter, "Explanation and Metaphysical Controversy", c. 1985 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Reck, Andrew, "The Realism of Roy Wood Sellars", 1970 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Reichenbach, Hans, "The Freedom of Will", c. 1956 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Reix, A., "Review of Naturalism and Ontology and Pure Pragmatics and Possible Worlds", c. 1980 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Rescher, Nicholas
      - "Aristotle's Doctrine of Future Contingency and Excluded Middle", c. 1962 (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - "Can One Infer Commands from Commands?", c. 1963 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - "Conceptual Idealism", c. 1971 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - The Coherence Theory of Truth, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 13-15)
      - "Distributive Justice", c. 1963 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - "Elements of a Logical Theory of Commands", c. 1964 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - "The Equivocality of Existence", c. 1975 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - "Evaluative Metaphysics", undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - "Fundamental Problems in the Theory of Scientific Explanation", 1963 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - "New Light from Arabic Sources on Galen and the Fourth Figure of the Syllogism", 1964 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - "A New Look at the Problem of Innate Ideas", c. 1965 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - "On the Logic of Chronological Propositions", c. 1963 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - "On the Prospects of Scientific Progress", 1974 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - "On the Rationale of Scientific Progress", c. 1973 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - "Plurality-Quantification", 1962 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - "Pragmatic Justification", 1963 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - "Truth and Necessity in Temporal Perspective", c. 1967 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - "Venn Diagrams for Plurative Syllogisms", c. 1962 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Rice, Philip, "Definitions in Value Theory", 1946 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Richards, Robert, "Sellars' Kantian Perspective on the Compatibility of Freedom and Determinism", 1973 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Richardson, Robert
      - "Materialism: The Elimination of the Mental", 1976 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - "Sense Impressions and Sensa: An Investigation of Sellarsian Scientific Realism", 1973 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Richman, Robert, "Sommers on Type Differences", 1968 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Robbins, Herbert, "A New Approach to a Classical Statistical Decision Problem", c. 1955 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Robinson, "The Legend of the Given", undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Rorty, Richard
      - "The Irreducibility of Substance", c. 1960 (Box 86, Folder 22)
      - "Privileged Representations", 1975 (Box 86, Folder 23)
      - "Realism and Reference", 1975 (Box 86, Folder 24)
      - "The Subjectivist Principle and the Linguistic Turn", c. 1962 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Rosenberg, Jay
      - "Apperception", 1978 (Box 86, Folder 26)
      - "Bergmann on Time - Showing and Saying", 1965 (Box 86, Folder 27)
      - "Comparing the Incommensurable: Another Look at Convergent Realism", 1987 (Box 86, Folder 28)
      - "The Concept of Linguistic Correctness", 1976 (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - "Confessions of a Heterodox Epistemologist", 1979 (Box 86, Folder 30)
      - "Conversation and Intelligence", 1979 (Box 86, Folder 31)
      - "Coupling, Retheoretization, and the Correspondence Principle", 1980 (Box 86, Folder 32)
      - "The Elusiveness of Categories, the Archimedean Dilemma, and the Nature of Man: A Study in Sellarsian Metaphysics", c. 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - "The 'Given' and How to Take It: Some Reflections on Phenomenal Ontology", 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - "Linguistic Roles and Proper Names", 1978 (Oversize 198)
      - "Naming and Contingency: Reflections on the New Modality", undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - "New Perspectives on the Tractatus", 1965 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - "On Strawson: Sounds, Skepticism, and Necessity", c. 1975 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - "On Understanding the Difficulty in Understanding Understanding", 1979 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - "One World and Our Knowledge of It", undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - "The Place of Color in the Scheme of Things: A Roadmap to Sellars' Carus Lectures", undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - "Russell and the Form of Outer Sense", c. 1972 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - "Transcendental Arguments Revisited", undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - "Wieso die Erkenntnislehre Nicht die Theorie des Wissens Ist, und was sie Stattdessen Sein Mag", undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - "Wilfrid Sellars' Philosophy of Mind", c. 1979 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - "Wittgenstein's Theory of Language", 1966 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Rosenthal, David
      - "Psychological Phenomena and Intentional Sentences", 1968 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - "Two Concepts of Consciousness", 1978 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Rottschaefer, William
      - "Marras' Critique of Sellars' Account of Thought: A Response", c. 1981 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - "Ordinary Knowledge and Scientific Realism", c. 1976 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - "Wilfrid Sellars on the Nature of Thought", 1982 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Rozeboom, William
      - "Empirical Realism and Classical Semantics", c. 1958 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - "The Factual Content of Theoretical Concepts", undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - "The Factual Equivalence of Scientific Theories", c. 1952 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - "In Defense of the Notational System of 'The Logical Typology of Psychological Variables'", c. 1956 (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - "Intentionality and 'Existence'", c. 1952 (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - "Just Before the Battle, Mother", 1958 (Box 87, Folder 24)
      - "The Logical Typology of Psychological Variables", c. 1956 (Box 87, Folder 25)
      - "Notes on Wilfrid Sellars' 'Grammar and Existence'", 1958 (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - "Of Selection Operators and Semanticists", 1960 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - "On the Factual Equivalence of Theories", 1959 (Box 87, Folder 28)
      - "Ontological Induction and the Logical Typology of Scientific Variables", c. 1960 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - "A Reaffirmation of the Intervening Variable: Hypothetical Construct Distinction", c. 1955 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Russman, Thomas, "The Problem of the Two Images", c. 1975 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Sagoff, Mark, "Descartes: The Objective Existence of Ideas", c. 1974 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Salmon, Wesley
      - "Clocks and Simultaneity in Special Relativity", c. 1973 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - "Inductive Inference", c. 1963 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - "On Vindicating Induction", 1961 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - "Partial Entailment as a Basis for Inductive Logic", c. 1968 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Sayre, Kenneth,Cybernetics and the Philosophy of Mind, ,1971 (Box 88, Folder 9-10)
    - Sayre McCord, Geoffrey,Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Schacht, Richard, "A Commentary on the Preface to Hegel's Phenomenology of Spirit", c. 1966 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Schaffner, Kenneth
      - "Space and Time in Lorentz, Poincare, and Einstein", c. 1972 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - "The Watson-Crick Model and Reductionism", 1969 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Scheffler, Israel, "Comments on Wilfrid Sellars' Paper", 1963 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Scheurer, Paul,Miscellaneous papers, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Schiller, Ralph, "Interpretations of the Quantum Theory", c. 1960 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Schlesinger, George
      - "It is False that Overnight Everything has Doubled in Size", c. 1962 (Box 88, Folder 18)
      - "The Problem of the Evil and the Problem of Suffering", 1964 (Box 88, Folder 19)
      - "The Two Notions of the Passage of Time", undated (Box 88, Folder 20)
      - "The Unpredictability of Free Choices", 1974 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Schmaus, Warren, "Comte's Views on the Role of Mental Imagery in the Formation of Hypotheses", 1979 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Schneewind, J. B.
      - "Concerning Some Criticisms of Mill's Utilitarianism, 1861-1876", 1973 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - "Moral Problems and Moral Philosophy in the Victorian Period", undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Schneirla, T. C., "Comparative Psychology", 1959 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Schultz, Robert
      - "Syntax and Style in the Languages of Film", undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - "Sense and Reference in the Languages of Art", 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Scriven, Michael
      - "Definitions, Explanations, and Theories", undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - "A Study of Radical Behaviorism", c. 1955 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Seebohm, Thomas, "On the Deduction of Categories", c. 1976 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Sedey, Daniel, "Hans Reichenbach's Theory of Token-Reflexivity", 1969 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Seibt, Johanna
      - "Properties as Processes: A Synoptic Study in Sellarsian Nominalism", undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Untitled, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Shapere, Dudley
      - "The Character of Scientific Change", 1979 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - Review of The Structure of Scientific Revolutions, c. 1962 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - "Space, Time, and Language", c. 1963 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Shapiro, Theodore, "Psychoanalysis, Philosophy, and the Public", 1985 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Sharpless, Seth, "Epistemology and the Language of Physiology", 1955 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Shaver, Robert
      - "The Fourth Paralogism", 1985 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - "Naturalism and Moral Skepticism", 1985 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Shea, Joseph, "Possible Lives and Types of Happiness in the Nocomachean Ethics", 1985 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Shimony, Abner
      - "Is Observation Theory-Laden?", 1969 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Untitled, c. 1966 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Shoemaker, Sydney, "Sameness of Experience", c. 1970 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Shwayder, D. S.
      - "Metaphysics", undated (Box 90, Folder 7-8)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Sicha, Jeffrey
      - "The Linguistic Theory of A Priori", c. 1961 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - "Logic: The Fundamentals of a Sellarsian Theory", 1977 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Metaphysics of Elementary Mathematics, undated (Box 91, Folder 1-5)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1970s (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - "On CantASTAplaNEDAniz", c. 1983 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Pure Pragmatics and Possible Worlds: The Early Essays of Wilfrid Sellars,untitled (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Quantification and related topics, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - "Reply to the Reader", 1971 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - "Sellarsian Realism", c. 1988 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - "Sicha on Marras", undated (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Siegel, Armand, "Objective Reality in Physics as a Limit Concept", c. 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Simon, Herbert
      - "Does Scientific Discovery Have a Logic", 1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - "Ramsey-Eliminability and the Testability of Scientific Theories", 1973 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Simon, Robert, "An Indirect Defense of the Merit Principle", c. 1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Skyrms, Brian
      - "An Immaculate Conception of Modality", c. 1976 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1967-1980 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - "Presuppositions of Induction", 1981 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - "The Problem of Future Contingencies", c. 1962 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Sleigh, R. C.
      - "Chisholm on Leibniz's Law in Epistemic Contexts", 1968 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - "Information Concerning Leibniz Scholars in the United States and Canada", 1980 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Smart, J. J. C.
      - "Causal Theories of Time", 1968 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - "Difficulties for Realism in the Philosophy of Science", c. 1978 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - "Explanation", 1964 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - "Materialism", 1963 (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - "Philosophy and Scientific Plausibility", 1963 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - "The Reality of Theoretical Entities", 1956 (Box 92, Folder 16)
      - "Sellars on Process", c. 1980 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      - "Some Comments on the Papers", 1964 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Smullyan, Arthur,Atlanta remarks on language, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Sober, Elliot, "Panglossian Functionalism and the Philosophy of Mind", c. 1981 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Sobocinski, Boleslaw
      - "Lesniewski's Foundations of Mathematics", undated (Box 92, Folder 21)
      - "Philosophy Seminar", 1950 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Solomon, Robert, "Hegel's Epistemology", 1973 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Solomon, William David, "Sellars' Defense of Altruism", 1978 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Sosa, Ernest
      - "Fates and Faces of Epistemology", 1981 (Box 92, Folder 25)
      - "Hypothetical Reasoning", 1967 (Box 92, Folder 26)
      - "Quantifiers and Beliefs and Sellars", 1969 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Stalnaker, Robert, "A Semantic Analysis of Conditional Logic", c. 1964 (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Steinmann, Martin, "Plato and Poetry: Divine Madness and Censorship", 1948 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Stengel, Barbara, "Understanding G. E. Moore's 'Some Judgments of Perception'", 1979 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Stevenson, Leslie
      - "Things in Themselves, Explanation, and the Mental", c. 1979 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - "Three Kinds of Transcendental Idealism", 1981 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - "Wittgenstein's Transcendental Deduction and Kant's Private Language Argument", 1979 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Stich, Stephen, "Could Man be an Irrational Animal?", 1980 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Strawson, P. F.
      - Review of The Definition of Good, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - "A Logician's Landscape", 1955 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - "Truth", undated (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Studdiford, Walter, "Probing Personality Structure: Phenotypic and Genotypic", 1962 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Sukale, Michael, "Perception, Knowledge and Contemplation", 1976 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Suppe, Frederick, "On Epistemic and Non-Epistemic Seeing", undated (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Richard, "Deliberation and Foreknowledge", 1962 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Teller, Paul, "Review of Ontological Relativity and Other Essays", 1971 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Tennant, Neil
      - "Evolutionary Epistemology", 1982 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - "In Defense of Evolutionary Epistemology", 1982 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Terrell, D. B., "Franz Brentano's Axiology: Some Corrections to Mr. Kubat's Paper", 1958 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Thalberg, Irving, "How Does Agent Causality Work?", 1975 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Thomason, Richmond
      - "Deontic Logic and the Role of Freedom in Moral Deliberation", 1976 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - "Deontic Logic as Founded on Tense Logic", 1971 (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - "Indirect Discourse is not Quotational", c. 1975 (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - "Modal Logic and Metaphysics", 1967 (Box 93, Folder 22)
      - "Modality and Reference", c. 1967 (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - "Semantics, Pragmatics, Conversation, and Presupposition", 1973 (Box 93, Folder 24)
      - "Some Extensions of Montague Grammar", 1972 (Box 93, Folder 25)
      - "Some Methodological Remarks on Semantics", 1976 (Box 93, Folder 26)
      - "Supervaluations, The Bald Man, and the Lottery", 1973 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Thomson, Judith, "Promises", 1980 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Tisza, L., "The Conceptual Structure of Physics", c. 1961 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Tomberlin, James
      - "A Note on the Identity Theory", 1964 (Box 93, Folder 30)
      - "Some Recent Work in Action Theory", 1976 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Toulmin, Stephen
      - "Concept-Formation in Philosophy and Psychology", 1959 (Box 93, Folder 32)
      - "From Logical Analysis to Conceptual History", 1966 (Box 93, Folder 33)
      - "Ludwig Wittgenstein Revisited", c. 1968 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Trenholme, Russell, "A Critique of Sellars, Quine, and Davidson on Language", 1969 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Tsugawa, A., "Speech Acts, Illocution and Literary Discourse", 1978 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Tu, Chi-Liang, "Was R. W. Sellars a Materialist?", 1981 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Turnbull, Robert
      - "The Argument of Plato's Parmedides", undated (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - "The Argument of the Sophist", 1962 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - "Aristotle's Categories", 1974 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - "Aristotle's Debt to the 'Natural Philosophy' of the Phaedo", 1956 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - "Aseity and Dependence in Leibniz's Metaphysics", 1958 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - "Becoming and Intelligibility", 1986 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - "A Brief Study of 'Imagination' in Kant's Critique of Pure Reason'", 1948 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - "The Causal Role of 'Sense Impressions:' Reflections on Sellarsian Themes", 1979 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - "Empirical and A Priori Elements in Broad's Theory of Knowledge", 1955 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - "'Engagement' and the Aboutness of Concepts", 1955 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - "Episteme and Doxa: Some Reflections on Eleatic and Heraclitean Themes in Plato", 1978, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - "Imperatives, Logic, and Moral Obligation", undated (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - "Knowledge and the Forms in the Later Platonic Dialogues", 1978 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - "The Later Platonic Concept of Scientific Explanation", c. 1971 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - "Linguistic Analysis, Phenomenology, and the Problems of Philosophy", 1964 (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - "'Natural Science' in the Later Dialogues of Plato", 1983 (Box 94, Folder 19)
      - "Ockham's Nominalistic Logic: Some Twentieth Century Reflections", c. 1960 (Box 94, Folder 20)
      - "On What There Is: Representation and History", 1984 (Box 94, Folder 21)
      - "Physics I.1: Sense Universals and First Principles", undated (Box 94, Folder 22)
      - "Plato: The Soul and Its Place in Nature", c. 1979 (Box 94, Folder 23)
      - "Platonic and Aristotelian Science", 1986 (Box 94, Folder 24)
      - "Plato's Concept of Scientific Explanation", undated (Box 94, Folder 25)
      - "Posterior Analytics II, Chap. XIX: Sense Perception, Universals, and Intuitive Knowledge", 1971 (Box 94, Folder 26)
      - "Predication: An Historical Sketch of Some Major Philosophical Patterns", 1981 (Box 94, Folder 27)
      - "Some Reflections on Heidegger's 'Vom Wesen der Wahrheit'", c. 1948 (Box 94, Folder 28)
      - "Some Reflections on J. Owens' 'The Grounds of Universality in Aristotle'", c. 1951 (Box 94, Folder 29)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
      - "What Plato Said in Parmenides", 1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - "Zeno's Stricture and Patterns of Predication in Plato, Aristotle, and Plotinus", 1981 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Tye, Michael, "The Adverbial Theory: A Defense of Sellars Argument Against Jackson", 1975 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Unger, Peter, "On Being Given More Than Skepticism", 1973 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Vander Veer, Garry, "Scientific Materialism", 1971 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Van Fraassen, Bas
      - "Bub on the Completeness of Quantum Mechanics", undated (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - "Construction of Papper Probability Functions", c. 1970 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - "Critical Notice: Hilary Putnam's Philosophy of Logic", 1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - "Dearest Hermione: Stories and Verse", undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - "The Einstein-Podolski-Rosen Paradox", c. 1972 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - "Le Realisme Scientifique", undated (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - "Meaning Relations and Modalities", 1968 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - "Notes on Probabilities of Conditionals", 1972 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - "On the Radical Incompleteness of the Manifest Image", 1976 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - "Probabilities of Conditionals", 1973 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - "Theoretical Entities: The Five Ways", 1973 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Vaught, Carl, "Categories and the Real Order", c. 1977 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Verene, Donald Phillip, "Categories and the Imagination", 1978 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Vinci, Thomas, "The Myth of the Myth of the Given", 1984 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Vlastos, Gregory
      - "Minimal Parts in Epicurean Atomism", undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - "Zeno of Elea", 1961 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - "The Senonian Argument Against Plurality", 1957 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Von Wright, Georg Henrik, "Foundation and Justification of Action", c. 1976 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Wagner, Michael
      - "Plotinus' World", 1982 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - "Realism and the Foundations of Science in Plotinus", 1982 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Walen, Alec, "Kant on Color", undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Wallace, William A., "Elementarity and Reality in Particle Physics", 1966 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Walsh, W. H., "Third Thoughts on the Second Analogy", undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Warburton, Peter
      - "Intentionality and Information Processing Machines", 1964 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - "Toward a Philosophical System: Values in an Age of Science", 1964 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Watanabe, Satosi
      - "A Mathematical Explication of Formation of Classes of Objects", 1962 (Box 96, Folder 8-9)
      - "A Probabilistic View of Formation of Concept and of Association", 1961 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - "'Reply' to Dr. A. E. Woodruff's Presentation on Philosophical Aspects of Quantum Field Theory", 1961 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - "Toward a Mathematical Theory of Knowledge", undated (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Wartenberg, Thomas
      - "Knowledge, Power, and Social Relations", 1980, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - "Perceptual Truth in Kant", 1976 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - "Poverty and Class Structure in Hegel's Theory of Civil Society", 1980 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - "'Species Being' and 'Human Nature' in Marx", 1980 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - "Value as an Ontological Concept", 1981 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Waxman, Wayne, "Kant's Logical Idealism", 1983 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Weimer, Walter, "On the Methodological Indispensability of Common Sense", c. 1969 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Weller, Cass, "Questions in and Around De Anima II.5", c. 1979 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Wells, Rulon
      - "A Priori Knowledge", undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - "Empiricism and the A Priori", undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - "Sentences as Denoting Truth-Values", 1950 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - "The State and Prospects of Semantics", 1950 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Wilcox, John, "How Much Do Young Philosophers Publish?", 1976 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Wilder, Hugh, "Practical Reason and the Logic of Imperatives", 1979 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Wilkin, James Jeffrey
      - "Function-Signs in the Tractatus", c. 1978 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - "Jumblese and Nominalism", c. 1974 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Will, Fred L.,Untitled, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Donald, "Form and Matter", 1957 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Fred, "Effability, Ontology and Method", 1981 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Kent
      - "The Indispensability of Truth", 1969 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - "A Note on Significant Contrast Arguments", undated (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Kirk Dallas, "Towards a Formal Reconstruction of Kant's Modal Functions of Judgment", c. 1974 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Margaret D.